A Finding Aid to the Jud Fine and Barbara McCarren Papers, circa 1968-2009, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
Jud Fine and Barbara McCarren papers
circa 1968-2009
Archives of American Art
Fine, Jud
McCarren, Barbara
AAA.finejud
Archival Resource Key
16.7 Linear feet
0.345 Gigabytes
The papers of sculptors Jud Fine and Barbara McCarren measure 16.7 linear feet and 0.345 Gigabytes, and date from circa 1968-2009. The majority of the collection falls into project files, with other series including correspondence, writings, personal business, printed material, photographic material, and artwork.
Biographical / Historical
Jud Fine (1944- ) is a sculptor and educator in Venice, California, as well as former director of the University of Southern California Roski School of Fine Arts. Jud Fine is married to fellow artist, sculptor and installation artist Barbara McCarren (1958-), born in Washington, D.C., and they maintain a studio where they work on projects and commissions both individually and collaboratively.
Born in Los Angeles, Fine received a BA in History from the University of California, Santa Barbara. With a limited artwork portfolio he was lucky enough to be accepted into the Masters of Fine Arts program at Cornell University. Fine's reputation as an artist took hold firmly in the late 1960s and early 1970s, becoming particularly well known for sculpture and mixed media drawings, which established a recognizable style and conceptual framework. He has been represented by Ronald Feldman Gallery in New York City since 1972. He has participated in solo and group exhibitions internationally at institutions including Museum of Contemporary Art, Los Angeles, Los Angeles County Museum of Art, Chicago Art Institute, Museum of Contemporary Art, Chicago, Guggenheim Museum, New York, Yale University Art Museum, Museum Stuki, Poland, University of Sidney, Power Art Institute, Australia and the Pushkin State Museum of Fine Art, Moscow. McCarren received her bachelors of arts degree at UCLA in1980 and would meet Fine during work towards her masters of fine arts at USC in 1986. After nearly a decade of pursuing solo career opportunities including public art commissions, they decided to join forces making collaborative project proposals as McCarren Fine.
As Mccarren/Fine they have executed several works including Waterline a two square block mixed use development in Huntington Beach, CA, Split Mound for the San Francisco Zoo, Mais a 23-acre interactive park in Long beach, CA, Modestopo, the civic center plaza for the City of Modesto and Stanislaus County, CA and both the Central Library and Pershing Square in downtown Los Angeles. Beyond public art commissions, their collaboration has extended to their studio practice, with collaborative exhibitions including a 2002 show in Bangkok, Thailand, that was later expanded with new work for the 2005 show, Currency, at Ronald Feldman Gallery, New York. Together McCarren/Fine have completed around thirty public work projects, and numerous studio projects.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged as seven series:
Series 1: Correspondence, circa 1970-2001 (0.5 Linear feet: Box 1)
Series 2: Writings, circa 1968-2003 (0.5 Linear feet: Box 1)
Series 3: Personal Business, circa 1969-2001 (1 Linear foot: Box 2)
Series 4: Project Files, circa 1988-2009 (14.4 Linear feet: Boxes 2-20; Oversize 21; 0.345 Gigabytes: ER0001-ER0005)
Series 5: Printed Material, circa 1974-1992 (0.2 Linear feet: Box 16)
Series 6: Photographic Material, circa 1970s-2000 (0.1 Linear feet: Box 16)
Series 7: Artwork, circa 1980s (1 Folder: Box 16)
Scope and Contents
The papers of sculptors Jud Fine and Barbara McCarren measure 16.7 linear feet and 0.345 Gigabytes, and date from circa 1968-2009. The majority of the collection falls into project files, with other series including correspondence, writings, personal business, printed material, photographic material, and artwork.
Correspondence is mostly professional in nature and is largely from Jud Fine's early career in the late sixties through the 1970s. There is also come McCarren/Fine correspondence starting in the 1990s as well as some correspondence regarding Barbara McCarren's solo career.
The writings series is comprised primarily of Jud Fine's writing practice associated with his earlier career, including notes and journal entries, lectures by Fine, as well as manuscripts for catalog essays and artist publications, an interview from 1984, and writings on Fine by others.
The personal business series includes exhibition files as well as gallery files containing sale and consignment paperwork, as well as daily business of the studio, primarily pertaining to Jud Fine's earlier career, with some documents pertaining to Barbara McCarren's solo career from the 1990s on.
Project files document various public art works and commissions taken on or applied for by McCarren/Fine, as well as solo projects that date before and after their formal collaboration in 1996. These documents include correspondence, contracts, reports, meeting minutes, renderings and other plans, notes, photographic material and research material, some of which is in digital formats.
Printed material includes various promotional materials for McCarren/Fine and solo projects for Barbara McCarren and Jud Fine, as well as a graphic design magazine publication, and a monographic catalog for a Jud Fine exhibition from 1974. Photographic material includes miscellaneous snapshots and snapshot albums, some of Fine and McCarren, in the studio and with artist friends, as well as an untitled album with study images of a strelitzia plant.
Artwork includes a single, unsigned painted work on canvas that has been cut awat from the frame or support.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research. Access to original papers requires an appointment and is limited to the Archives' Washington, D.C. Research Center.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated in 2022 by Jud Fine and Barbara McCarren.
Public art -- United States; Sculptors -- California -- Los Angeles; Educators -- California -- Los Angeles; Installation artists -- California -- Los Angeles; Interviews
- Correspondence, circa 1970-2001; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 0.5 Linear feet Box 1
  Scope and Contents
  Correspondence is mostly professional in nature and is largely from Jud Fine's early career in the late sixties through the 1970s. There is also come McCarren/Fine correspondence starting in the 1990s as well as some correspondence regarding Barbara McCarren's solo career.
  - Art Institute of Chicago, School of, circa 1974-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A, circa 1974-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - B, circa 1976-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - C, circa 1976-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Lucrezia de Domizio, circa 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - D, 1985-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - E, 1976-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ian Hamilton Finlay, circa 1975-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - F, circa 1972-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - G, circa 1980-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - H, circa 1979, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Irish Museum of Modern Art, Dublin, circa 1995-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - I, 1981, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - J, circa 1974-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - K, circa 1976-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Los Angeles Museum of Art, circa 1972-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - L, circa 1972-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - M, circa 1976-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Ohio State University, circa 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - O, circa 1975-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Pearce Institute, Glasgow, circa 1994-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Randy Putnam, circa 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - P, circa 1973-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Gerry Rosen, circa 1975-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - R, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Silpakorn University Art Center, American Thai Exchange, circa1998-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Stedelijk Museum, circa 1974-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - S, circa 1977-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Tracks Journal, circa 1975-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - T, circa 1987-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - W, circa 1973-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Mail Art, circa 1973-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Unidentified / First Name Only, circa 1970s-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Writings, circa 1968-2003; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 0.5 Linear feet Box 1
  The writings series is comprised primarily of Jud Fine's writing practice associated with his earlier career, including notes and journal entries, lectures by Fine, as well as manuscripts for catalog essays and artist publications, an interview from 1984, and writings on Fine by others.
  - MFA Thesis and Show Description (1970), circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Statement on Eclecteria, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Words, Amsterdam, Agia Galini (1974), circa 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Or, an Introduction Language and Structure Reporoduction, Nova Scotia College of Art and Design, circa 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Slide Lecture, Ohio University School of Art (Apr. 8, 1975), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Confessions (1976), circa 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 39-40)
  - Miscellaneous Artis Statements, circa 1980s-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Miscellaneous Project Descriptions, circa 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - A Conversation Between Jud Fine, Francis Colpitt, and Michael H. Smith, circa 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Notes on Oceanic Navigation, circa 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Notes and Journals, circa 1968-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 45-49)
  - Writings by Others, "Telling Acts: The Art of Jud Fine", circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Writings by Others, "Vision Concept and Object: The Art of Jud Fine 1971-1985" by Robert L. Pincus, circa 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Personal Business, circa 1969-2001; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 1 Linear foot Box 2
  The personal business series includes exhibition files as well as gallery files containing sale and consignment paperwork, as well as daily business of the studio, primarily pertaining to Jud Fine's earlier career, with some documents pertaining to Barbara McCarren's solo career from the 1990s on.
  - Artwork, Drive (1995), circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Artwork, Mary Stuart's Ravishment Descending Time, Side Street Projects (McCarren), circa 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Art Reference Listings, circa 1974-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Australia Visit (Lecture, Exhibition), circa 1977-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Commission, California State Arts Commission (with Peter Shelton, Mark Lere, and Lloyd Hamerol) Exposition Park, Los Angeles, circa 1982-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Commissions (Charles Hack vis Ronald Feldman Fine Arts, Inc.), circa 1978-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Exhibitions, Archival Resource Key
    - Documenta 5 (June-Oct. 1972), circa 197291977; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Southern California Attitudes (Sep.-Nov. 1972) Pasadena Art Museum, Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Biennale de Paris (Sep.-Oct. 1973), circa 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Edinburgh Arts Festival, Richard DeMarco Gallery (1974), circa1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Sarah Lawrence College (Sep.-Oct. 1975), circa 1973-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Jud Fine: Confessions and Related Work (Sep. 1976) California State University, Fullerton, circa 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Jud Fine Drawings, Santa Barbara Museum of Art (may-June 1978), circa 1977-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Jud Fine: Works From Shime / Stone (Jan.-Feb. 1982) Virginia Commonwealth University, circa 1981-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Sculpture 82 (Mar.-Aug. 1982) Sonoma State Univeristy, circa 1981-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Sculpture Sacramento )Sep.-Oct. 1982), circa 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Arena for Museum of Seasonal Change Landmark Art Projects (Apr.-May. 1987), circa 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - La Jolla Museum of Contemporary Art (Aug.-Oct. 1988), circa 1986-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Botanica, Tweed Museum of Art (McCarren), circa 1999-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Knowing Limits, Pratt Institute (Feb.-Mar. 2000), circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous Exhibition Documents, circa 1981-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Grants, General, circa 1976-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Galleries and Museums, Archival Resource Key
    - Alan Brown Gallery, circa 1977-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - GSA Public Buildings Service, circa 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Baxter Art Gallery at Caltech, circa 1980-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - California International Arts Foundation, circa 1982-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Dayton's Gallery 12, circa 1973-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Jose Barrio Gallery, circa 1975-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Los Angeles Institute of Contemporary Art, circa 1974-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Margo Leavin Gallery, circa 1975-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Marianne Deson Gallery, circa 1976-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Riko Mizuno Gallery, circa 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Ronald Feldman Fine Arts, Inc., circa 1972-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Thomas Segal Gallery, circa 1982-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Wita Gardiner Associates, circa 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Sales, Invoices and Receipts, circa 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Teaching Applications, circa 1969-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Teaching, Speaking Engagements, circa 1976-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Insurance, circa 1982-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Packing, circa 1982-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Paystubs, circa 1983-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Printing (Douglas M. Parker Studio), circa 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Public Art Projects, Early, circa 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Publications, Jud Fine Artist Publications, circa 1976-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Project Files, circa 1988-2009; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 14.4 Linear feet Boxes 2-20; Oversize 21; 0.345 Gigabytes ER0001-ER0005
  Project files document various public art works and commissions taken on or applied for by McCarren/Fine, as well as solo projects that date before and after their formal collaboration in 1996. These documents include correspondence, contracts, reports, meeting minutes, renderings and other plans, notes, photographic material and research material, some of which is in digital formats.
  - Alhambra Gateway Walk, Archival Resource Key
    - Correspondence, 2005-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Fabrication, circa 2004-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Fabrication Delay, 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Concept, Public Art, circa 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Contract, 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Gate Inset, circa 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Proposal (July 2005), circa 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Invoices, circa 2005-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Irving's Gate Text, 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Notes, circa 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Research Material, 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Panel Files, circa 2005-2006; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital records; see ER0001. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Alhambra Panel Files, Digital Documents, 2005, 2006; Archival Resource Key; 0.019 Gigabytes 12 computer files (Folder ER0001)
    - Photographic Material, circa 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Artspark Los Angeles, Children's Museum Design Competition, circa 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 14-15)
  - Atlanta, Hartsfield Airport, Art Proposal, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Atlanta, Sam Nunn Federal Center, Archival Resource Key
    - Proposal, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Notes, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Research Material, Fountains, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Research Material, Langston Hughes, Lorraine Hansberry, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - CalTech Labyrinth Proposal, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Carlsbad Arts Office Stagecoach Park Proposal, circa 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Carnation Company, Glendale, Archival Resource Key
    - Early Project Description, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Budget, circa 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Contract, circa 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Engineering, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Drawings, Notes, circa 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Cleveland State University, 17-18th Street Block Project, Archival Resource Key
    - Correspondence, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Budget, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Notes, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Colorado Place, Susan Rush Proposal, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Culver City Hall, Archival Resource Key
    - Correspondence, circa 1994-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Camera, circa 1994-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Design Cropping and Paste-Ups, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Drawings, Quotation Courtyard, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Contract, Proposal, circa 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Proposal, Rejection, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Maintenance, 1995, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Photographic Material, Source Material and Permissions, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Photographic Material, Fabrication, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Photographic Material, Set of Images, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Press Clippings, circa 1992-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Text Copy, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Research Material, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Eureka, Department of Education, Sacramento, Archival Resource Key
    - Correspondence, circa 2001-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Architecture, circa 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Budget, circa 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Contract, circa 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Installation, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Project Plans, circa 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Chameleon, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Foucault's Pendulum, circa 2000-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Plumb Bob Plans, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Serpentine, circa 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Text Design, circa 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Photographic Material, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Maintenance, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Pendulum Repair (Jan., Mar. 2003), circa 2002-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Notes, circa 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Research Material, circa 2000-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Firstar Block, Hamm Plaza, St. Paul Riverfront Corporation, Archival Resource Key
    - Correspondence, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Budget, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - SRF Consulting, Inc., 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Site Redevelopment Program Brochure, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Design Team Composition, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Hiawatha Corridor Aesthetic Design Guide, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Land Survey Maps, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Plans and Drawings, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 2-3)
    - Notes, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Photographic Material, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Photographic Material, Negatives, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Research Material, Postcard Images, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Research Material, circa 1998-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - HUD Building Washington D.C., Archival Resource Key
    - Correspondence, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Meeting Notes, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Research Material, Notes, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Los Altos Center Public Art Project, Archival Resource Key
    - Contract, circa 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Contract, Pricing, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Budget, circa 1995-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Construction, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Expenses, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Drawings and Notes, circa 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Interns, CSU Long Beach, circa 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Midden, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Puvunga Plaza Plaque, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Release Forms, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Technical Addendum, circa 1994-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Tuscan Column, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 34)